historic progressive fell for an award incoming ken klippenstein said mom dami is privately
telling hakeem jeffrey's primary challenger not to run against him per new york times
now i've been seeing folks running with this like she's a runner she's a track star
and i'm trying to understand now y'all know i'm as objective as it gets
i don't endorse anything but truth and i'm gonna tell you now y'all look foolish jumping on this
when you see that the source is the constant source of anti-progressive anti-leftist pro
zio bs like i don't even understand how that math maths for you and the person that they're saying
that he's saying this to is chiyose who we know are their peoples now i hope it's not true
i also know there's not enough here for me to assume that it is so can we just like stop jumping
to every conclusion there is quite enough to make content about without making very possible lies
for the new york times something that we need to actually amplify cut it out
listen to your people
billionaires